Shimamura is just Shimamura.
And in my heart, I think she'll
always just be Shimamura.
I don't really get it, but it's definitely reassuring.
Knowing that, I can let my guard down.
What a wonderful thing.
Ah, I thought you might turn up again.
And who might this be?
This is the Shimamura.
What does that even mean?
Oho, so it's you...
So, uh... what's your name?
Unlike my foolish compatriot,
I have come prepared with a name!
You may call me Chikama Yashiro.
I've come to Planet Earth
in search of my compatriot.
Your what?
Compatriot? Oh, like a friend?
Wait, there's more of you?
No, hang on, did you just say "Planet Earth"?
My compatriot came to this planet on a mission—
however, they have yet to return.
Therefore, I set out in search,
but it appears that I have landed
in the wrong location.
Alrighty then.
You go ahead and enjoy discussing
the unknown with them.
What?
Oh, my fish-dar is picking up
some readings over there!
Hey!
Sneak-sneak-sneak.
That Hino. So the real reason
you invited me fishing was...
So you're the one known as Shimamura, are you?
Huh? Uh... yeah.
I hear you're so popular that
the natives come in droves to see you.
Yeah, I'm definitely not that Shimamura.
No need to be modest.
Ah, yes. I am no native.
I have come from the future.
Just so we're clear.
Sure, and I've come from the past.
Nice to meet you.
You appear an ordinary earthling.
Sure looks that way.
Why don't you take that thing off?
My face is not quite ready,
so I would appreciate your patience.
What, is your face going to be delivered
from a bakery or something?
Shouldn't you be looking for your friend,
or rather, your compatriot?
Well, when the stomach is empty...
Is this philosophy?
I have already confirmed that my compatriot is safe,
so I considered a break reasonable.
So they contacted you?
Well, something like that.
If you can contact them,
then can't you just go meet up?
There are reasons as to why we cannot!
I-I see.
Plop.
Nothing's biting, huh?
That's a fantastic mindset.
Yeah?
When nothing's biting, nothing's going to plan.
That means you've started something.
You just felt like doing that?
Fishy!
Heck yeah!
All we can do from here is hope for a bright future,
and cast our lines.
So yeah, that happened.
Huh.
Am I boring you?
No, you're not.
Could you not be so passive-aggressive?
Sorry, my bad.
Are you tired?
Well, work was pretty hectic yesterday.
Wait, you have a job?
Where?
Not telling.
Why not?
Because I know you'd show up if I did.
Well, duh.
Then no. It's embarrassing.
No, it's not.
The fact that you're working is admirable.
Adachi once said that I was like a cat.
Keeping my distance from others
makes me cat-like, it seems.
I guess there's a part of me
that doesn't want to open up to people.
But Adachi's basically the same.
Adachi dozing off with her head on my lap
definitely reminded me of a cat.
What is it?
I prefer this way, I think.
Oh, really?
Yeah, this way I can catch your scent.
What? Wait, do I have B.O.?
That's not what I meant.
Fine, I won't.
Shimamura, you're not classy at all.
Classy. Hmm... classy, huh?
Yeah, I don't think anyone's told me that before.
Say, Adachi.
Wanna go to class together after lunch?
Where'd that idea come from?
Well, there's a minimum required attendance.
Basically, it'd be more fun
if we became second-years together.
Together...
I guess every now and then's fine.
All right!
Then hey,
let's go somewhere after class.
Do you have plans already?
Not today.
Honestly, I barely ever do.
I see.
Maybe I'll actually get a bite today.
High school is its very own, unique society,
so bringing those elements outside of it can be weird.
So it makes sense why some people
would prefer to simply live here.
But regardless, I want to land a better future.
And if I don't cast my line, nothing's gonna start.
How were your classes?
History was good, but I don't know
how to do math anymore.
I don't know either and I've been
to class way more than you,
so where does that put me?
You caught a lot of eyes today, Shimamura.
Nah, I'm pretty sure that was you.
No, you were the one getting attention.
It's probably because you're so pretty.
Huh?
What's wrong?
It's just that I've never been called pretty before, so...
Really? Not even by, say... your boyfriend?
I've never had one.
I guess everybody's blind, then.
What?
Wait, where's your bike?
It's out for repairs.
Huh... So you actually walked to school. Well done.
I thought maybe you'd be here.
R-Right.
Mm, sugar!
Are you going to classes tomorrow, Shimamura?
Well, I want to try to stick with it—
for at least three days or so.
I see.
What say you, Adachi?
Shall we soldier on together?
Sure, a few more days couldn't hurt.
Want a bite?
Sure, thanks.
Let me return the favour.
Adachi?
Oh, I get it.
Here you go. You wanted the cream, right?
Oh, all right then...
Where should we go after we finish eating?
Being with others seems
to bring burdens along with it.
Figuring stuff out, dealing with problems.
Trying to mend relationships — or breaking things off.
But then, when you wade through all the negativity,
sometimes you stumble across a bit of happiness.
Like finding that ball you lost as a kid.
I want to believe that meeting Adachi
is changing my future for the better.
Um...
I-If you don't like it, I'll let go! Like, right away!
No, I just wasn't expecting it.
Should I stop, then?
It's no biggie. Let's go.
Didn't pick you for the clingy type.
I'm not...
I'm just surprised is all.
Well, I'm not...
...that surprised.
Hello there.
Oh, uh... hey.
I saw you in the area, so I thought I would greet you.
You really walk around town in that, huh?
Of course — this is my finest attire.
There is a wonderfully sweet smell
emanating from your fingertips.
Yes, this is fantastic! What is it!
Probably doughnuts, since we were just eating them.
Doughnuts?
What do you think you're doing...
and how did I know you'd try?
There's a blip on my dough-dar!
There are doughnuts in there, are there not?
Yeah, but don't grab at them.
If you give me one of those d-doughnuts,
I shall reveal one of the secrets of the universe!
Secrets of what?
Listen, these are for my little sister.
If they eat a doughnut, they'll take off
their helmet, and I'll see their face.
Pop.
Fine, you can have one.
All right then, this one.
Oh, so this is a doughnut!
You're not taking off your helmet?!
Munchy... Gulp.
Plop.
This is incredible! It's so sweet, so incredibly sweet!
You've never had a doughnut before?
What kind of dance is that?
Do you have any more sweets?
Buy some yourself.
I don't have any money!
How do you survive?
Shimamura.
I'm going to get my bike.
Huh?
Later.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Wait, was she mad?
Would you rather learn what just happened
instead of a secret of the universe?
Go nuts.
She's jealous because she didn't get a doughnut!
Go home.
Will meeting this self-proclaimed
time traveller change my life?
I have no idea.
But nothing can really change your life's course.
No one knows what their future holds anyway,
so how can you change it?
Man, relationships are hard...
I totally understand.
Like hell you do.
For some reason, Shimamura thinks
that I'm the more attractive one.
If you ask me, she couldn't be more wrong.
I think that Shimamura is much prettier.
Her dreamy eyes, the way she modestly moves her lips...
My eyes are always drawn to her face.
Especially her lips.
I had a dream that Shimamura and I kissed.
It's not like I'm into her that way.
I think I just want to be closer with Shimamura.
So it's definitely not like that.
That kiss didn't mean anything.
Nope! Nothing!
I'm not saying I'd never kiss her...
But that doesn't mean I actively want to... I think?
If there was no one else within
a 5-kilometre radius from Shimamura,
and she was in an enchanted sleep and
an omniscient deity just happened to reassure me
that she wasn't going to wake up for 24 hours,
maybe, just maybe, after hour 23,
I'd kiss her once to relieve some boredom.
Huh? Wait...
But I don't swing that way.
I just want to be special to Shimamura.
I want to be the first person
she thinks of when she hears "friend".
I'll admit that sounds a bit possessive.
To be quite honest,
I've been wondering just how much
Shimamura actually likes me.
Am I on the same level as her other friends?
Or do I mean more to her than that?
Welcome to—
Huh?
Aha...
I told you it was embarrassing.
It's fine. It looks good on you.
Ah, a friend.
Now that she's in high school,
she never brings any friends over.
Yeah...
Just ignore her.
Oho... Are you two in the same class?
Mom, stop it.
Oh, come on!
Mom... Let's just order already.
I'll have the Dandan noodles!
Then I'll have...
Apparently, Shimamura
doesn't really understand me,
but it's the same thing here.
She doesn't push me away when I rely on her,
but she doesn't try to rely on anyone herself.
That was how I perceived her.
"Just when I thought she'd
cleaned up her act, here we are again!"
Who's that supposed to be?
The homeroom teacher.
He asked me why you weren't in class —
like, how should I know?
What?
I was just thinking about how cute
you looked last night.
Huh? I mean, you're pretty cute too.
What? But I didn't dress up or anything.
Maybe I'll go eat there again.
Don't. Please don't.
Just kidding.
I don't know if I'd go there again with my family.
It is sort of embarrassing
when you're with family—
Hey, it's Shimamura!
Huh? Oh, so you are here today.
Can I sit next to you?
Uh, sure...
Um, you're... Right?
It's Adachi! A-da-chi.
You forgot her name but thought
mumbling under your breath would work?
So, Adachi.
Huh?
Good morning.
G-Good morning.
It's rare to see you two eat caf food.
I guess I don't mind this.
My dear mother overslept this morning.
I could get used to how noisy
things are with them around.
It takes me back to lunchtime in grade school.
But it also felt like they were cutting into
my time alone with Shimamura.
I can't deny that this all felt kind of wrong.
Adachi, what are you going to do this afternoon?
I'm going to class... I think.
Gotcha.
Shimamura.
Could I maybe...
come over to your house today?
This way.
Okay...
Welcome home, Big... sis.
Sorry to intrude...
Hey.
Oh, this is my friend. From yesterday.
Yeah...
Sorry...
Don't worry about her.
She's just shy.
So your room's on the first floor.
Yeah.
You can sit wherever.
There we go.
So, what should we do?
G-Good question.
Hey, uh, Shimamura?
Hm?
Don't say it, don't say it, don't say it...
Um, do you mind if I sit?
Huh?
Like, between your legs or something.
What did I just say?!
Oh god, now she'll think I'm a total weirdo.
Sure, I don't mind.
She doesn't mind?!
Wait, huh? I...
It's fine?
Is this a dream? I'm dreaming, right?
It's really fine?
Shimamura's legs...
What are you doing?
Well, uh...
There!
Huh? Hello?! What?!
My little sister likes to sit like this. Isn't it normal?
Y-Yeah, sure...
It's weird. It's super weird!
Um...
My collarbone hurts!
What's up?
Usually, people feel pain inside their chest,
but I'm feeling it my bones themselves.
So do you have a boyfriend?
What do you think?
No...?
I can hear them grinding, like they're gonna pop out.
You're right. Actually, we had
this same conversation yesterday.
Oh right.
I just wish I could relax.
Do you have one, Adachi?
I don't...
Gotcha.
And all of a sudden I knew...
what would settle my nerves.
I think I like you.
Wait, what?
What was I about to say?
Wait, did I say it?
I really think I like you.
Now I've done it.
God, I'm such an idiot.
This is... this is... this is...
I-I think I like you...
Probably, maybe.
You know, like, really like.
I'm a complete idiot.
Um... You okay?
Are you breathing? Your face is, like, bright red...
What the frap...
What the fraaaaap?!
Ow! Ow, ow... My neck hurts. It hurts.
The sun will set and rise like always,
but will a normal day ever dawn for me again?
Adashimapedia: Aliens!
We are aliens.
Isn't it weird for aliens to call themselves "aliens"?
That's a good point!
They should be more specific, like:
"We are boobliens. Let us fondle your ti—"
Time to kick you aliens outta here.
We've been defeated...