You see students skipping class on the rooftop
all the time in manga and stuff,
but if you actually took a nap up there,
you'd get a sunburn like no other.
I think it's about time for
everybody else to start third period.
I've pretty much always skipped classes,
and Adachi rarely ever came to school.
We met up here by chance
and ended up spending a lot of time together.
Is it okay if I serve next?
I guess...
Huh?
What?!
I looked that one up online last night.
I don't have a racket at home though,
so I practiced with a rice paddle.
No fair, you can't throw a curveball at a newbie!
If you lack the drive to improve,
that's not my... fault!
When we're skipping class like this,
we can usually sense if the other is here.
I've only got like a ten percent success rate for now.
So we usually come up and find each other.
So you're getting worse...
Let's do this!
I guess third period was P.E.
What if they come up here?
Shall we open the windows and jump for it?
What? We're two stories up!
Wouldn't we break our legs?
Ah, I see. So you're calcium-deficient.
I dunno how you got that idea.
Dang. This is kind of exciting.
I don't think they realize we're up here, though.
Maybe I'll drink some milk with my lunch today,
so my legs don't break if we ever have to jump.
I see — you've decided to strengthen your bones.
Those moments where it was like nothing else mattered...
always felt so nice.
Ugh, I can't anymore.
It's way too hot!
Wanna go outside?
It's almost lunch anyway.
My, how lewd.
Our school's...
Um...
Dignity?
Yeah, that! Our school's dignity is at stake here.
So what are we doing for lunch?
Yeah, yeah. We can't have you go out in that state.
Fine, I'll go.
I'll go next time.
Yeah right. That's what you say every time.
Oh yeah, so I'll get you a danish, as per usual,
but should I also get a milk today?
Water, thanks.
Gotcha!
Hup.
Being Adachi's partner in crime is pretty fun.
Is it because it's Adachi that I got hooked,
or do I just get a rush from breaking the rules?
The answer's obvious, but...
Let's leave it up in the air for now.
What's she even doing?
Shimamura was already here
when I first came up to the gym's second floor.
She still looked like a middle schooler,
so I figured she was a first-year like me.
A-Adachi, was it?
Yeah?
Um, we're in the same class.
Oh, right.
My friends call me by my surname, Shimamura.
Like the clothing store?
Do you come here often?
I just happened to stop by today. You?
Same here.
They're so loud.
Right?
Hi-yah!
Oh.
You're gonna touch it?
Cicadas aren't too bad.
Think it'll stay?
How many days do you think it has left?
Dunno.
Yeah.
How much longer do you want it to live?
Fifteen days... give or take.
Fifteen days later,
Shimamura's hands were covered in dirt
when she came up to the second floor.
And that's how she and I first met.
Adachi!
I got you the last danish.
And here's your water.
Thanks.
Back then,
I didn't consider Shimamura my friend yet.
Of course there's a book for it.
Dang, that's expensive.
Hey, it's Shimamura.
Hino.
Whatcha lookin' at?
Smash! You joining the table tennis club, Shimamura?
Hino is a classmate who's sort of a plain Jane.
No, I was just curious.
She's never dyed her hair,
or even shoplifted.
Curious? You randomly picked
a book about ping-pong?
She's apparently never ended up in a catfight
with a girl from another school, either.
Hey!
Jeez, I was wondering where ran off to,
but here you are chatting with Shimamura.
This other classmate, Nagafuji,
is your usual glasses girl with big boobs.
That pretty much sums her up, I guess.
So what were you talking about?
Her big boobs and her big attitude
make her pretty mature...
Don't worry about it.
All right then, I won't.
but she's a bit dense.
Hino, do you have an excuse
for that blatant sexual harassment?
Nagafuji is too self-conscious,
so I thought I'd lighten the mood.
Really?
When they're this big, the boys are always staring.
Of course I'm self-conscious.
I'm sure all the boys in class staring at your boobies
have fondled them at least ten times in their minds.
That's super gross.
That's the price of greatness, my lady.
Whoops, my hand slipped.
Apparently, Hino and Nagafuji
have been friends since they were little.
I only became friends with them in high school,
so they're closer to each other than to me.
But when it comes to distance,
it's not like being closer to someone is always better.
If you get too close, you might fight
and have misunderstandings.
Oh, yeah. The other day at the fishing hole
there was someone in a spacesuit...
Hey, look over there!
I think relationships with others
are like free diving.
Hey, who was that girl?
Wasn't she in our class in, like, April?
You say that like every time we see her.
Her name is Adachi.
She's our classmate.
And she's a certified delinquent —
teacher-approved.
Huh?
Is she a friend of yours?
Who knows?
You keep sinking deeper and deeper,
and things start disappearing around you.
You struggle to breathe, so you try
to get back to the water's surface.
And then you poke your head out for some air
before sinking deeper yet again.
If you keep repeating that cycle...
Morning.
Adachi...
Hey, you're late today.
Oh, I...
I thought I'd just head home,
but I heard a ping-pong ball bouncing.
I saw you yesterday.
Yeah, I guess you did.
Where's your bag?
Left it with my bike.
Right.
Well, I'm heading home.
Okay...
Hey, Adachi.
"Let's go to class together today."
or "Let's walk home together today."
Which would you prefer?
Huh?
Um...
Okay then. I'll just go kill time
somewhere until school's over.
Sorry for the wait!
You didn't have to sit in the exact same position.
Sorry you got caught in the rain.
Well, it's not like you did a rain dance.
So which way's your house?
This way.
Oh, I thought so.
Here, hold this.
It's just that it's a pretty big detour from my house.
I live that way.
So whose place should we go home from?
That's not a question you hear every day.
Then... let's head to your place first.
All right.
Riding double like this is against the law, you know?
Yeah, and we're delinquents.
Good point.
Man, being delinquents rules.
It sure does.
I guess you do have friends, huh?
Huh?
Oh, you mean Hino and Nagafuji?
I thought you were always up there
because you were lonely.
What about you, Adachi?
Got any friends?
Probably just you, really.
Wow, that's sad!
Killing time outside of school
and then going home together is weird.
It's definitely weird,
but the idea of it is appealing and exciting.
If either of us was an honour student, they'd say,
"We shouldn't be doing this!"
...or something.
They'd try to correct the other's ways
with the power of friendship.
But we're both pretty irresponsible,
so we're just dragging each other down deeper.
I go through here, and then...
to get back to my house...
That's a pretty decent walk.
Shimamura!
Here, I got you a towel.
Thanks.
Sorry.
Huh? For what?
For making you come all the way here.
Want me to give you a ride home?
Huh? That'd make the whole ride here pointless.
I guess.
All right, I'm headed home.
Yeah, I'll probably see you tomorrow.
When I looked down at Adachi's head
from the back of her bicycle,
I thought her hair, usually so pretty framing her face,
looked like some kind of fluffy animal.
Maybe I'd look the same way.
What a weird day.
See? I told you there were noises
coming from upstairs.
Huh? I guess you really were playing table tennis.
Oh crap.
Wow, way to make a friend feel valued.
Shimamura...
Adachi.
So, how'd you know I was here?
I remembered the table tennis
book at the bookstore.
Ah, shoot.
So that's Adachi, is it?
I think that's pretty obvious, but yes.
Oh, yes. Adachi.
You guys were friends?
Yeah, I guess so.
Then yesterday — well, whatever.
I'm Nagafuji.
I'm Hino.
Nagafuji and Hino... Got it.
Nice to meet you.
Uh, I brought us some bread!
I'm surprised they never caught you guys during PE.
We stay pretty quiet whenever there's a gym class.
Which one do you want, Adachi?
Whatever you like is fine.
Hm... Okay then, this one!
Are you free on Sunday, Shimamura?
This week? I think so.
Wanna go to the fishing hole, then?
That kid in the spacesuit
I was telling you about is a riot.
Aren't you just asking me to go fishing with you?
No, no. That's just a bonus.
They took a particular interest
in you when I brought you up.
Why don't you just take Nagafuji with you?
I have club stuff.
Come on, let's go!
Sure, why not?
Heck yes!
Okay, we're going to the fishing hole on Sunday.
The next day, Adachi didn't turn up.
There was a lot I didn't know about Adachi,
and that frustrated me at times.
The only person I could understand even slightly...
was myself.
After seeing Hino and Nagafuji
having a blast up here yesterday,
I realized that was never what I wanted.
Adachi might not show up again for a while.
Worst-case scenario, I might not
see her again until graduation.
I might not...
That would be the worst...
not seeing Adachi.
Blam!
Huh?
A-Adachi?
Sorry...
I was planning to stop just short.
But I couldn't brake in time.
I'm pretty sure I heard you say "Blam!"
Wait, are you sure about this?
About what?
Well, your house isn't this way.
Yeah, but...
Yeah, you're right.
Shimamura, here.
Huh? Wait, what?
I was going to give them to you during lunch today.
Lunch?
Oh, so this is "next time".
I'm glad you weren't going home
with your other friends.
I wouldn't have been able to give them to you.
What?
Oh, nothing.
Adachi had said that I was her only friend.
So I think I get the picture.
This was about all I could ask,
and this was all Adachi was able to say right now.
Hey, Adachi.
You're walking me all the way home, right?
Yeah, that's the plan.
Look at me! I'm a plane! Neaoow!
The slight elation that I felt
had given me wings.
I wonder how many steps it'll take
before embarrassment sets in.
So what's Adachi like, anyway?
What's she like? Um, normal?
That explains nothing, Shima-moo.
I don't know how much I should tell you.
Adachi likes water, preferably mineral water.
It doesn't seem to matter which brand.
I see. So Adachi is a Namekian.
I haven't seen her regrow
any limbs yet, though. Also...
Anything biting?
The spacesuit stuck out
like a blindingly white sore thumb.
Suddenly, a small astronaut stood before me.
Adashimapedia: Ping-Pong!
Differentiate table tennis and ping-pong.
Ping-pong's for fun. Table tennis is serious business!
So serious ping-pong?
That's table tennis!
And fun table tennis?
That becomes ping-pong!
Ping-pong is but table tennis.
What now?
I tried to sound philosophical.