At midday, when time stands still
Our hearts can't seem to stop racing
I'm always the one rushing it
Leaving scattered thoughts under the sun
It all shines so bright
Does it shine for you?
We're close, yet so far
Who needs labels anyway?
We may have a typical future coming
But our present is a treasure
It'll be the time of our lives
So hey, why won't you smile?
What's got to give, how long will it take?
When will us being together be the usual?
We all let our fears take over and betray us
I see tears behind that pure mask
Time to get ready for class like usual
And this day we share
Each brilliant, perfect moment
A whole world of feelings to embrace
So I'll be waiting
Running ahead and waiting for you
I'll be waiting here again today
I'll be by your side