In this wonderful world, since the day we met
Everything seems so full of joy
And I start to feel like I can do anything I dream
So stay by my side
The future feels so unreal
Like an endless stretch of colourless days
But there's a place here with you
In our own little world, caressed by the sunlight
We're a hair's breadth apart
Breathless, aching to touch?
Reality crashes down when we break apart
So don't let go
In this wonderful world, when I see you along my path
I find myself falling in love
And I start to feel like I can do anything I dream
Every time a new breeze blows
Sometimes the feelings keep me awake at night
But I want to stand up
I want to break free
And stand under the clear sky together with you